<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jim Withington</title>
    <link>http://www.jimwithington.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jim Withington</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Jim Withington</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jimwithington.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for a New Engine</title>
      <link>http://www.jimwithington.com/2017/07/07/new-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 14:54:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimwithington.com/2017/07/07/new-engine/</guid>
      <description>I decided to build (Un)focused Dev in WordPress, thinking that doing so would make me do a lot more WordPress dev.
I was wrong.
All it did was frustrate me, much like I thought it would.
So I&amp;rsquo;m back in Staticland, this time using Netlify and Hugo.
I get to work using the JAMStack, a way of working I&amp;rsquo;m pretty stoked about.
Things around here are a bit broken right now, as I figure out silly things like &amp;ldquo;where&amp;rsquo;d my images go when I zapped them from Digital Ocean?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I’ve been doing; or, what if you start a project and it kinda takes off but doesn’t; or, what if it seems like you abandoned your own thing; or, integrating new practices; or, Day 36 to Day 64</title>
      <link>http://www.jimwithington.com/2017/03/19/what-ive-been-doing-or-what-if-you-start-a-project-and-it-kinda-takes-off-but-doesnt-or-what-if-it-seems-like-you-abandoned-your-own-thing-or-integrating-new-practices-or-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 05:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimwithington.com/2017/03/19/what-ive-been-doing-or-what-if-you-start-a-project-and-it-kinda-takes-off-but-doesnt-or-what-if-it-seems-like-you-abandoned-your-own-thing-or-integrating-new-practices-or-day/</guid>
      <description>-- For the first 5 weeks or so of 2017, I committed a whole lot to my #100DaysOfHealthing repo. The project buzzed around my head, I set up my work computer to launch Git Bash every day when I logged in, and folks that I admire even added me to their own projects.
And then hey look at that, it was February, and a lot of good things were happening in my personal life&amp;#8211;health things shaking out, finances slowly but kinda surely improving, meditating every day (not just three minutes at a time, but 10 minutes, even!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Days of Healthing</title>
      <link>http://www.jimwithington.com/2017/01/02/100-days-of-healthing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 01:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimwithington.com/2017/01/02/100-days-of-healthing/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;#8217;s this, now? Inspired by 100DaysofCode, 100 Days of Healthing is a challenge to spend an hour a day, for 100 days, working on your health &amp;amp; self care. It&amp;#8217;s permission to give yourself an hour a day. And we&amp;#8217;re all here with you.
Why do you hate 100 Days of Code? Oh my goodness, that&amp;#8217;s so not true! I don&amp;#8217;t. I think it&amp;#8217;s a fabulous concept, super motivating, something I want to do (maybe for the second 100 days of 2017?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a New WordPress Blog With Digital Ocean</title>
      <link>http://www.jimwithington.com/2016/11/13/starting-a-new-wordpress-blog-with-digital-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 05:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimwithington.com/2016/11/13/starting-a-new-wordpress-blog-with-digital-ocean/</guid>
      <description>Starting a New WordPress Blog With Digital Ocean I launched this today and I did it with a few hours worth of work. Some considerations:
 I&amp;#8217;m actually super into jekyll and static site generators in general. However, I&amp;#8217;m going to be helping with a project soon that might use WordPress, and I&amp;#8217;m also pretty interested in it in general. So, here we go! I&amp;#8217;m comfy using tutorials for command line stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.jimwithington.com/post/2019-01-31-literally-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jimwithington.com/post/2019-01-31-literally-speaking/</guid>
      <description>Date: 02/02/19 Title: Literally Speaking Permalink: /literally-speaking Tags: learning, coding
Literally speaking Yesterday I put in a pull request for the framework that we use at work. It was related to an issue I&amp;rsquo;d submitted; namely, that I wanted to be able to send folks style guide links to specific variants of components we build. {{more}} Building this had a lot of codey type things in it:
 Thinking about how to build it took longer than building it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>